cleanmyspace.com 2018-12-23

# Privacy Policy - Clean My Space

The following Privacy Policy discloses Clean Digital Productions Inc.’s practices and policies regarding the gathering and dissemination of personal information.

Personal Information We Collect

When you visit our website, use our contact form, or sign up for our newsletter, there is some personal information that may be collected from you. That information may include:

  * your name, phone number and email address
  * account preferences, including whether or not you wish to receive our newsletter and website update information by email
  * any other information you voluntarily send to us through our website contact form

This information is collected and used for a number of purposes:

  * To provide you with the information you have requested, and to keep you informed with respect to ongoing changes to our website. Your email address will be used to send you our newsletters and mailings IF YOU HAVE REQUESTED US TO DO SO. You can withdraw your consent for such mailings at any time by contacting us as set out below.
  * To manage and administer our web presence. The nature of the Internet is such that it passively and automatically collects certain information about a user’s traffic patterns, which may be linked to their Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. These are unique Internet addresses assigned to all Web users by their Internet Service Providers (ISP). Server logs record statistical information, such as visitors’ IP addresses, type of operating systems, time and duration of visit, web pages requested, and identify visitors by categories such as domains and browser types. These statistics are only used on an aggregate basis and will not contain any information that could identify you personally.
  * To meet legal, regulatory, security, and processing requirements (such as in response to a court order), and otherwise as permitted or required by law.

If we intend to use personal information for purposes not identified to you or as set out above, these other purposes will be described to you at the time of collection or before using the information. We will not use your information for any other purpose without your consent.

## Third Parties’ Access to Information

Clean Digital Productions Inc. is not in the business of selling customer information to others. Our customer information is not available for sale to any outside entity. We contract with third parties to fulfill certain functions on our behalf, such as providing marketing assistance, analyzing data, preparing and maintaining site content, hosting site content, and providing customer service. These agents have access to customer information only as required in order to help them perform their functions on our behalf, but they are not allowed to use that information for any other purpose and must keep such information confidential.

Clean Digital Productions Inc. will release customer information to the appropriate law enforcement, governmental, or other authorities if legally required to do so.

## External Links

The Clean My Space website may contain links or references to other websites to which this Privacy Policy does not apply. These sites are not owned or controlled by Clean Digital Productions Inc., and Clean Digital Productions Inc. is not responsible for the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information or the privacy practices of other organizations or other websites to which our site may refer visitors or provide links for. When submitting personal information on such other websites, we encourage you to read the privacy policies and terms of use of those sites.

## Non-Secure Website Areas

You should be aware that if you voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information (e.g., email address) on non-secure areas of the Clean My Space website, that information can be collected and correlated and used by third parties and may result in unsolicited messages from third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of Clean Digital Productions Inc.

## Security

We store email newsletter subscriber information in a secure manner on servers in the US. These servers are operated by Mailchimp (specifically The Rocket Science Group LLC d/b/a MailChimp, a State of Georgia limited liability company). Only authorized employees of this 3rd party along with employees, agents, and affiliates of Clean Digital Productions Inc. who require access to your personal information in order to fulfill their job or contractual requirements will have access to your personal information to the extent necessary to fulfill such requirements.

**Opt-Out Option**

Upon request, Clean Digital Productions Inc. will allow any user to opt out of further contacts at any time. Also, upon a user’s request, Clean Digital Productions Inc. will use commercially reasonable efforts to functionally delete the user and his or her personal information from our database; however, it may be impossible to delete a user’s entry without some residual information because of backups and records of deletions. You can email us at info [@] cleanmyspace [.com] to request that your information be deleted from our servers. You may also unsubscribe at any time using its “unsubscribe” link provided in all correspondence.

## Your Consent

Consent to the collection, use and disclosure of personal information may be given in various ways. Consent can be express (e.g., orally, electronically or on a form you may sign describing the intended uses and disclosures of personal information) or implied (e.g., when you provide information necessary for a service you have requested, or in some circumstances where notice has been provided to you about our intentions with respect to your personal information and you have not withdrawn your consent for an identified purpose, such as by using an opt out option provided). Consent may be given by your authorized representative (such as a legal guardian or a person having a power of attorney). Generally, by providing us with personal information, we will assume that you consent to our collection, use and disclosure of such information for the purposes identified or described in this Privacy Policy, if applicable, or as otherwise described at the time of collection. You may withdraw your consent to our collection, use and disclosure of personal information at any time, subject to contractual and legal restrictions and reasonable notice, however, please note that if you withdraw your consent to certain uses of your personal information, we may no longer be able to provide certain of our products or services.

Clean Digital Productions Inc. does not collect, use or disclose your personal information other than as described in this Privacy Policy without your consent, unless permitted or required by law. We may be required or permitted under statute or regulation to collect, use or disclose personal information without your consent, for example in response to a court order or subpoena, to comply with local or federal regulations.

## Contacting Us

This website is subject to the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act. This legislation closely regulates our handling of your personal information. You can find more information on this Act through the Government of Canada website, http://www.canada.gc.ca. You have a right to know what information we have on file about you. If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, or if you would like to review your personal information, you can contact us:

**By Email:  
**privacy@cleanmyspace.com

**By Post:  
**_Clean Digital Productions Inc._  
Attn: Privacy Officer  
PO Box 20045 Southbrook PO  
Maple, Ontario  
L6A 4M4

Any dispute arising between the customer and Clean Digital Productions Inc. with respect to privacy is subject to the terms and conditions of use and this Privacy Policy, including limitations on damages, arbitration and application of the laws of the Province of Ontario, Canada. The foregoing policies are effective as of November 1, 2014. Clean Digital Productions Inc. reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the policy changes on our website. Site visitors are advised to periodically check this website for such changes.
